# ANA TRIPUNOSKA ZDRAVKOVIKJ

# Front-End Developer

(M) +389 70 777 044

atripunoska.github.io

atripunoska@gmail.com

# **PROFILE**

Passionate and meticulous front-end developer with over 5 years of front end experience, striving for continuous self-improvement and making the internet a better (looking) place. Primary focus on converting data to graphical interface for users to view and interact with that data, through digital interaction using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER

March 2016 - Present

#### **IWM NETWORK**

- Using markup languages like HTML to create user-friendly web pages
- Maintaining and improving websites
- Collaborate with back-end developers and web designers to improve usability
- PSD to HTML
- Developing custom WordPress Themes
- Developing custom Liferay Themes
- Developing e-commerce websites using WooCommerce for selling products online
- Strong experience with Responsive website design
- Implementing On-Page SEO

#### **INTERN**

August 2015 - September 2015

#### **IBORN.NET**

- Maintaining Web Applications
- Designing mobile based features
- Writing functional required documents and guides

# INTERN

September 2014 - May 2015

# **DUNA COMPUTERS**

- Maintaining Web Applications
- Creating Web Application with Bootstrap
- Creating CSS files for websites and assist web developers in effective implementation
- Testing websites and reporting bugs

#### **INTERN**

January 2013 - February 2013

# KOMERCIJALNA BANKA

- Managing the database
- Writing SQL queries to insert, modify and delete data in database

# **EDUCATION**

# **SKILLS**

#### **TECHNICAL**

HTML/HTML5 CSS/CSS3 JAVASCRIPT BOOTSTRAP LESS/SASS WORDPRESS GIT PHOTOSHOP WOOCOMMERCE PHP

**PERSONAL** 

TEAM WORK
WORK ETHIC
ADAPTABILITY
PROBLEM
SOLVING
COMMUNICATION
LISTENING

#### **LANGUAGES**

# **MACEDONIAN**

NATIVE

# ENGLISH

BILINGUAL

#### **SPANISH**

CONVERSATIONAL - LEVEL A2

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

CAMBRIDGE ENGLISH: FIRST (FCE)
GRADE B

ONLINE MARKETING FUNDAMENTALS 2018

# **PUBLICATIONS**

TRIPUNOSKA, ANA & STOJANOV, RISTE & GRAMATIKOV, SASHO. (2021). "ANALYSIS AND GUIDELINES FOR IMPROVING THE CURRENT STATE OF ACCESSIBILITY OF MACEDONIAN WEBSITES FOR PEOPLE WITH DISABILITIES"

# MASTER OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

2018 - 2021

- FACULTY OF COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING SS. CYRIL AND METHODIUS UNIVERSITY